Guide to the Stanford University, Michelle R. Clayman Institute for Gender Research, Records SC0705
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Accession ARCH-2004-215
  - Publications--Working Papers
    - Equal Protection: Feminist Perspectives--Deborah Rhode (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Perspectives on Professional Women--Deborah Rhode (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Woman's Point of View--Deborah Rhode (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Women in Leadership and Implications for Affirmative Action--Stansbury, Thomas, Wiggins (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Toward a General Theory of Occupational Sex Segregation: The Case of Public School Teaching--Myra Strober (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - The Scope of Microeconomics: Implications for Economic Education--Myra Strober (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - The Dynamics of Occupational Segregation among Bank Tellers--Myra Strober and Carolyn Arnold (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - The Feminization of Public School Teaching: Cross-sectional Analysis, 1850-1880--Strober & Lanford (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - The Present-minded Professor: Controlling One's Career--Shelley Taylor and Joanne Martin (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - The Measure of Pleasure: Peter of Spain on Men, Women, and Lovesickness - Mary Wack (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Gender Differences in Role Diffentiation and Organizational Task Performance--Henry Walker & Mary Fennell (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Mixed Metaphors: Native and Anthropoligical Models of Gender & Kinship Domains--Sylvia Yanagisako (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Toward a Unified Analysis of Gender and Kinship--S. Yanagisako and J. Collier (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Defining Feminism: A Comparative History Approach--Karen Offen (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Deborah Rhode--Stanford Memos (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Divorce Conference Papers-11-1988 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Numerical List: Working Paper (Insert to Publication List) (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - WP #1 Segregation by Gender in Public School Teaching--Myra Strober (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - WP # 2 Chicanas in Postsecondary Education--Maria Chacon (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - WP #3 Beyond Liberal and Marxist Leninist Feminism--Sylvia Wynter (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - WP #4 Sexual Harrassment: A Selected Bibliography--Margaret Ctuikshank (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - WP #5 Feminism and Kinship Theory: A Conference Report--Tsing & Yanagisako (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - WP #7 Token Status: Prejudices & Discrimination Revisited--Northcraft and Martin (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - WP #8 What Price Change? The Great War and Englishwomen's Diaries - Blodgett (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - WP #9 Publishing by Academic Lesbians--M. Cruikshank (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - WP #10 Martial/Marital: The Patriarchal Significance of War--Mary Klages (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - WP #11 A Letter to Virginia Woolf. On Women and War--S. Lankford (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - WP #12 Clara Schumann: Artist and Woman--Nancy Reich (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - WP #13 The Mobilization of Women and Child Labor During WWII--Natsuki Aruga (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - WP #14 Women in Leadership and Implications for Aff. Act.--Stansbury, Thomas, Wiggins (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - WP #18 A Feminine Approach to Ethics--Nei Noddings (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - WP #19 Observations on Bereavement--Irvin Yalom (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - #20 In the Pipeline.. .(WISEST Project)--Zappert & Stansbury (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - WP #21 Their Canon, Our Arsenal--Lillian Robinson (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - WP #22 Toward an Historical Definition of Feminism: The Contribution of France--Karen Offen (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - WP #23 Mother to Herself: The Writer's Quest for Sanity--M. Yalom (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - WP #24 Shaping the Organizational Context for Minority Inclusion--Joanne Martin & T. Pettigrew (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - WP #25 Working Parents and the Problem of Sick Child Care--Karen Skold (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - WP #26 Toward a Feminist Recognition of an Androgynous Trinity--Neila Seshachari (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - WP #27 South Africa's Bantustan Policy: Its Impact on Women--Cherryl Walker (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - WP #28 A Virtuous Affair: The Correspondence Between Abigail Adams & James Lovell--E.B. Gelles (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - WP #29 The Abigail Industry: A Survey of the Literature About Abigail Adams --Edith Gelles (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - WP #30 Child Care Issues in the Divorcing Family--Charlene Depner (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - WP #31 Dynamics of Occupational Segregation by Gender: Bank Tellers (1950-80)--Strober/Arnold (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - WP #33 Gender Differences in Leadership and Influence in Small Groups - Walker and Fennell (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - WP #34 Salary, Job Satisfaction, & Stress Among Men and Women Managers --Arnold and Strober (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - WP #36 To Commit of Not to Commit Adultery: The Debate. Some Differences...- Annette Lawson (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - WP #37 Social Atoms: Working-Class Autobiography, Subjectivity & Gender --Regenia Gagnier (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - WP #38 Towards a Formal Theory of Gender Segregation--Cohen and Lockheed (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Mixed Metaphors: Native and Anthropoligical Models of Gender & Kinship Domains--Sylvia Yanagisako (did not get (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - WP #41 Association and Assimilation--Deborah Rhode (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - WP #42 Gender and Role Differentiation--Walker and Fennell (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - WP #43 Undoing Discriminati on: Job Integration & Comp. Worth--Wm. Bielby & James Baron (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - WP #44 The Structure of Opportunity: How Promotion Ladders Vary--Baron, Davis-Blake, Bielby (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - WP #45 Changes in the Educational and Career Plans of American High School Senior Women in the Past Quarter (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - WP #46 John Stuart Mill's Autobiography: Putting the Text into Context - Susan Groag Bell (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - WP #47 Women Create Gardens in Male Landscapes: A Revisionist Approach to 18-cent. Eng. Garden Hist.--Susan D..11 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - WP #48 Feminism in Italy--Lucia Chiavola Birnbaum (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - WP #49 Gender Roles in Social Movement Organizations--Rhoda Blumberg (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - WP #50 Future Trends in Women's Crimes and Women's Imprisonment--Pat Carlen (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - WP #51 Are the Prestige Structures of all Societies Male?--Jane Collier (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - WP #52 Theory in Anthropology Since Feminist Practice--Jane Collier and Sylvia Yanagisako (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - WP #53 Health Aspects of Aging: A Selected, Annotated Bibliography - Margaret Cruikshank (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - WP #54 Finding an Integrated Curriculum that Meets the Needs of Rural Women --Some Conclusions--J. Davison (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - WP #55 The Question of Safety: Quality Assurance; Standards and Equipment; Licensure and Accreditation - (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - WP #55 Collecting Oral Autobiographies of Non-Literate African Women--Jean Davison (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - WP #56 Free-Standing Birth Centers: A Viable Alternative--Pamela Eakins, Linda Jean May, J. Hopkins, & W.B. O'Reilly (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - WP #56 Gender Relations of Production in Collective Farming in Mozambique: Case Studies--Jean Davison (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - WP #57 Letter Writing as Therapy: The Case of Abigail Adams--Edith Gelles (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - WP #58 Gossip: An Eighteenth-Century Case--Edith Gelles (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - WP #59 Psychoanalysis, Female Ability and Mathematics--Ellen Gottheil (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - WP #60 The Promise of Prevention: Historical Perspectives on American Mental Health Services--Margo Horn (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - WP #61 The Birthless Birthgiver: Reflections on the Liturgy of Yeshe Tsogyel, The Great Bliss Queen--Anne C. Klein (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - WP #62 In Lieu of a Conclusion. Storfall: The Destruction of Utopia?--Anna K. Kuhn (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - WP #63 Psychosocial Predictors of Sport Participation in College-aged Women and Men--Sherri Matteo (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - WP #64 The Effect of Sex and Status on Casual Attributions for Success & Failure in Women's & Men's Crew Teams--S. (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - WP #65 Female Sexuality, Experimental Psychology, and Feminism: Presenting a Unified Picture--Sherri Matteo (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - WP #66 Defining Feminism: A Comparative Historical Perspective--Karen Offen (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - WP #67 Feminism in Nineteenth Century Europe: A Historiographical Overview --Karen Offen (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - WP #68 Women and the Politics of Motherhood in France, 1920-1940--Karen Offen (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - WP #69 Occupational Inequality--Deborah Rhode (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - WP #70 Definitions of Difference--Deborah Rhode (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - WP #71 The Perinatal Information Management System (PIMS) Birth Certificate...- Richwald, Levy, Lew, and (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - WP #72 Statistical Report on Five Calif. Free-Standing Birth Centers - Richwald, Levy, Lew (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - WP #73 The State and the Education of Women: Toward a Theoretical Understanding--Nelly Stromquist (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - WP #74 Adele Hugo, Witness of her Husband's Life--Marilyn Yalom (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - WP #75 George Sand's Poetics of Autobiography--Marilyn Yalom (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - WP #76 French Women's Autobiographies: 1793-1939--Marilyn Yalom (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - WP #77 The Ferninisation of Poverty & The Poverty of Penal Feminisation: An Analysis--Pat Carlen (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - The Varied Meanings of'Masculine' and'Feminine--Eleanor E. Maccoby - #86 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Chicanas and Chicanos: Barriers to Progress in Higher Educational--Chacon, Cohen, and Strover R #105 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Obstetric Outcomes at the Birth Place in Menlo Park: The First Seven Years --Pam Eakins #144 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - The Risk of Multiple Addictions Guidelines for Assessing a Woman's Alcohol & Drug Use--S. Matteo #162 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Body Politics: Women, Work, and the Politics of Motherhood in France, 1920-1950 Karen Offen #146 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - The California Wellness Foundation (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Administrative Guide (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Equal Rights Advocates (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Marriage in Old Age Translation by Charles and Carstensen (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Services--Organizations
    - Faculty Club (Services) (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Bon Appetit Catering (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Stanford Catering (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Caterers (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Event Services (AudioNisual Equipment) (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Facilities--Palo Alto locations (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Stanford Terrace Inn--Palo Alto (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Facilities--San Francisco locations (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Florists (Services) (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Publication Services (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - United Parcel Service (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Video Services (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Alumni Association--Stanford--Events Booklet (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Stanford University Trustees (Women) (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Board of Trustees (Stanford) (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Continuing Studies Program (Stanford) (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Department of Anthropology (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Hoover institution (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Humanities Center (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Stanford Associates (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Tape Closet (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Tapes/Duplicating (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - AAUW American Association of University Women (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - AAUW American Association of University Women 2 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Feminist Studies Resource Faculty (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Feminist Studies Program at Stanford (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - GWN Newsletter (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Graduate Women's Network (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - GWN (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - HUB Co-ventures for Women's Enterprise (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Margaret Sanger Papers Project (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - National Organization for Women (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Silicon Valley Tech Group--Michelle Clayman, Susan Nycum (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Stanford Professional Women Membership Directory (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Stanford Women's Center (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Women's Coalition for Gender Equity at Stanford University (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Women's Faculty Caucus Steering Committee (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - WFC--1998 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - WFC--4/16/98 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Women Faculty Caucus 96 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Women's Faculty Caucus 94-94 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Women's Heritage Museum (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Women's Yellow Pages (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Institute Folders/info. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Women's Caucus 1993-94 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Women's Caucus Addresses (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Women's Caucus Press Release and Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Women's Caucus Task Force (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Women's Caucus Sterring Committee and Ballot (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Stanford Women's Faculty Caucus (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Articles 1 Misc. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Misc. Rosters (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Women's Health Conference
    - Budget (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Autoimmune Book (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - SACWHP (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Women's Health (History) (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Somatization--Gender Differences (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Canadian Health Care System (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Computer (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Library (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - CSGWH (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - E M D ED Research (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - MSWHS (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Students Article (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - TWHP Archival (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Gleen's Presentation Re: Violence Against Women (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Stanford Participants (Workshop) 5-7-99 Seminar (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - 5/7/99 Seminar To Do (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - To: Stanford (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Stanford Med. School Curriculum (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Originals (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Berga (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - McEwen (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Rabin (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Schwartz (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Bios/Blurbs (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Logistics--Food, Hotel, etc. (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Other Invitees (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Review Paper--Workshop (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Background Papers--No (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Background Papers--Yes (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Potential Presenters--workshop (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Adresses (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Proceedings--Examples (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - To Do After Workshop (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Presenters (Lunches) (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Schedule (Lunches) (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Logistics--Food, etc. (Lunches) (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - To Do (Lunches) (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence (lunches) (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Attendees (lunches) (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - WHRC Info--Start-up plans & correspondence (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence WHRC organization (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Current Literature (purpose, mission) WHRC Info (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Women's Health Center of Excellence (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Journal of Gender Specific Medicine (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - WH Activities--Stanford CRWHRM (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - WH Activities--Stanford Women's Wellness (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - WH Activities--Stanford Reproductive Endocrinology (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - UCSF Center of Excellence in Women's Health (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Lilly Centre for Women's Health (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - UCSF / Stanford WH Researchers (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - WH Activities--NIH--NICHHd--Reproductive Sci. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - WH Activities--Columbia U. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - WH Activities--Commonwealth Fund (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - WH Activities--U. Penn (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - WH Activites--AAMC--Women in Medicine (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Industry / Technology (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Department of Health & Human Services (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Harvard Program in Ethics & the Professions (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Women's Health Research Internet Sites (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - WH Activities--Misc. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Fundraising WHRC--Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Fundraising WHRC--$ Received (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Fundraising WHRC--How To (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Fundraising WHRC--Foundations (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Grants Awarded (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Women & Autoimmunity (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Cardiovascular Disease (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Eating Disorders I body image (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Menopause/ HRT (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Women's Health Articles (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Fan Thank Yous (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Feminism/Women's Health/FP (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Feminist Studies (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Lesbian Health (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Iris Litt (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Summer Institute 1995 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Women's Health Forum--March 1994 BINDER (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Conference: HCWC Participants Roster (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Conference: HCWC Schedule of Events (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Conference: HCWC Co-Sponsors--CEWAER (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Conference: HCWC CEWAER (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Conference: HCWC CEWAER: Reports (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Conference: HCWC Background Info-press, Media (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Conference: HCWC Women's Health Forum (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Conference: HCWC Media/People (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Press Release Information (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Conference: HCWC Background Info--Misc, Other (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - CWH Forum Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Conference: HCWC Letters-Chron (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Conference: HCWC 1992 Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Conference: HCWC Question Form (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Conference: HCWC 4/25/94 Meeting Minutes (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Conference: HCWC 3/28/94 Women of Color Coalition Mtg. (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Conference: HCWC 1/3194 Meeting Minutes (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Conference: HCWC 7/6193 Meeting Minutes (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Conference: HCWC 6128/93 Meeting Minutes (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Conference: HCWC-05-1993 Meeting Minutes (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Conference: HCWC-01-1993 Meeting Minutes (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Conference: HCWC 11/16/92 Meeting Minutes (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Conference: HCWC 10/13/92 Agenda & Planning (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Conference: HCWC June 1992 Exec. Comm. Packet (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Conference: HCWC Scholarships (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Conference: HCWC The James Irvine Foundation (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Conference: HCWC U.S. Public Health Service (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Conference: HCWC U.S. Public Health Service Corresp. (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Conference: HCWC U.S. Public Health Service Contract (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Conference: HCWC Master Funder's List (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Conference: HCWC Most Likely Funders (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Conference: HCWC AAUW Community Action Grant (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Conference: HCWC Budget (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Conference: HCWC USPHS Women's Health Conference Reports (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Conference: HCWC L.A. Associates/Funding Ideas (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Conference: HCWC Funding Contacts--New (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Conference: HCWC Rooms, etc. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Conference: HCWC Program Schedule (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Conference: HCWC Hotels and Room Rates (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Conference: HCWC One-Page Summary (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Conference: HCWC Planning Dynamics (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Conference: HCWC Funding Leads -Old (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Conference: HCWC (Income) Account--General Gifts (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - HCWC: Income (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - The Upjohn Company (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Pfizer Labs (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Krames Communications (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Hewlett Packard/Barbara Waugh (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Stuart Foundations (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - HWCC: CHES Credits (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - HWCC: Conference Fact Sheet (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - HWCC: Press Release (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - HWCC: Housing (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - HWCC: Mailing Services (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - HWCC: Invitation (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - HWCC: Supporting Organizations 1 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - HWCC: Supporting Organizations 2 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - HWCC: Supporting Org. Author Form (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Conference HCWC: Save the Date Postcard (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Wyeth Ayerst Laboratories (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - San Jose Mercury News Article (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Campus Report Article (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Conference: HCWC Stanford Conf. Office (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Conference: HCWC Video Conferencing (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Conference: HCWC Campus Maps and Parking Permits (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Conference: HCWC Travel (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - HWCC: Mailing Lists (Lorraine) (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Conference: HCWC Mailing-Adress Lists and Labels (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - CA Coalition for the Future of Public Health (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Health Organizations--Planning Dynamics (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - HWCC: Male Legislators & Male Constitutional Officers (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - HWCC: Women Legislators & State Treasurer (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - ConferenceL HCWC Town Meeting Table (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Minority Breast Cancer Awareness (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Womancare Clinic (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Conference: HCWC Curriculum Vitae (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Conference: HCWC Speakers ( Potential ) (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - HWCC: Potential Keynotes (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Conference: HCWC Joycelyn Elders, MD (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Conference: HCWC Vivian W. Pinn, MD (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Jewelle Taylor Gibbs, PhD (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Bernadine Healy/NIH (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Conference: HCWC Special Invitees (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Conference: HCWC Regrets (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - HWCC: Speaker Information Form (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - HWCC: Kim Yeager (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Vitas (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Topics (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Forum: Health of CA Women of Color "Women and Aging" (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - HWCC: AIDS/STDs (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Forum: Health of CA Women of Color "Women and AIDS" (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - HWCC: Breast & Other Cancers (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - HWCC: Domestic Violence (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Forum: Health of CA Women of Color "Violence" (domestic) (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - HWCC: Holistic & Alternative Medicine (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - HWCC: Imn igrant Health (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - HWCC: Mental Health (Box 21, Folder 66)
    - HWCC: Aging (Box 21, Folder 67)
    - HWCC: Reproductive Health (Box 21, Folder 68)
    - Forum: Health of CA Women of Color "Reproductive Health" (Box 21, Folder 69)
    - HWCC: Substance Abuse (Box 21, Folder 70)
    - HWCC: How to Work with your Community (Box 21, Folder 71)
    - Conference: HCWC Media Day Media Contacts (Box 21, Folder 72)
    - People Expecting Summaries (Box 21, Folder 73)
    - Keynote Speakers (Box 21, Folder 74)
    - Town Hall Panel / Final Reports (Box 21, Folder 75)
    - Workshops (Box 21, Folder 76)
    - Summaries Sent in by Workshop Presenters (Box 21, Folder 77)
    - The Health of Women of Color Binder (Box 21, Folder 78)
    - The Health of Women of Color Binder (Box 21, Folder 79)
    - Cover Sheet, Participant eval. (Box 21, Folder 80)
    - Keynote Speakers (Box 21, Folder 81)
    - Friday Workshops (Box 21, Folder 82)
    - Saturday Workshops (Box 21, Folder 83)